[{"answer": "my friend, I really fuckin' hate McDonald's, man. Ever since they started in with the chicken, everything went downhill", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, man, if you could swing something there, I'd do anything for you. I want to work with you guys", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What class", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Where is he now", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Man.  They make you wear a fuckin' candy stripe suit over there", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Man.  They make you wear a fuckin' candy stripe suit over there", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Poor guy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The motherfucker pissed me off", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I didn't take that shit", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hearts, lungs, guts..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't know. Wherever you want", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " The point sounds fine", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How about the point", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " All right, the point it is", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Why can't you do it", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Your friends use the pool too", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I can see it all now. This is going to be just like the girl you fell in love with at Fotomat this summer. You bought forty bucks of fuckin' film and you never even talked to her", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Okay. Okay.  Here's what you do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Don't worry about it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "There... There's his car. I know he's at work tonight. He hasn't come into my friend's since he called my house. My mother told him I was still at high school, after I told him I was nineteen. I guess I should tell him I'm fifteen", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Does my friend care that you're seventeen", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What do you do with the jackets people leave here", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You keep them", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " I wanted to talk a little bit about school, if I could..", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "How often do you go", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "School.  School is no problem. All you have to do is go to get the grades. And if you know something, all you have to do is go about half the time", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't go at all", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Do you have Mrs. my friend for English", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah. She is pretty good", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's happening right now. I'm here at the Atlantis. Everything's fine except... I left my wallet at home", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No. It's too late. The food is coming and everything. my friend, I've got to ask you this favor, and I'll never ask you for anything again in this lifetime or any other. Will you please borrow your mom's car, go by my house, get my wallet, and meet me back here", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No. That's okay", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Naw. I don't mind", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Hey, slow down. This is my brother's car", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He is", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Listen to this... 'What are your mate's three most erogenous zones?", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Wouldn't penis and balls be the same category", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "This is how I dress all the time", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I thought I'd take it off for the drive over to that place. It's kind of uncomfortable", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I can't wait until I can drive next year. I walk every day. It's such a drag", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Sometimes I get a ride with my brother. But he usually works in the mornings, and then drives to school himself", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You're a really good kisser", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " No. Are you crazy", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What's wrong", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I guess I did", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "What's April 16th", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I didn't see you this morning", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I'm in a hurry too. I just thought I could say hi to you", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "What do you think it is", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "It couldn't be", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "It couldn't be", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Of course it was my friend. If it was my friend, you'd be out to here", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "There's only one thing we can do. We've got to get rid of it. We've got to get an abortion", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Yeah. My brother my friend got his girlfriend one once", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Doesn't sound free to me.  So you want me to pay for it", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Sevent", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I'm instructed to tell you that we are on a video alarm system and there are other hidden cameras in the store ..", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Okay.  I just started here, and they just taught me the procedure. I'll give you the money, just let me figure this out", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Where's my friend", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Not coming? What happened", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "But what are you going to do", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "that place?", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "And... you can only tell it's the right girl if you're sensitive", "docId": "Fast-Times-at-Ridgemont-High.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Sensitive is when you can tell how people feel without asking", "qsentId": 68}]